Peter Ehab

Software developer with 3 years of experience, seeks employment as part of a dynamic and creative software development team.

Saif st, Sidi Bishr, Alexandria (+20) 0155 5840 994 petereroshdy@gmail.com

SKILLS

Understanding of **Nodejs**, **Expressjs** and **MongoDB** application development with the knowledge of **Frontend** technologies, and familiarity with **MVC**, Plus understanding of open source projects such as **Wordpress**.

Experience in **Android** Development Native or Hybrid (**Flutter**).

Understanding of PHP and MySQL application development.

Experience in Laravel framework, With good experience in Git.

Experience working with **Linux** environment.

Knowledge of **PostgreSQL** and **Firebase** technologies.

Understanding of Third Party **APIs**, such Facebook, Google, Plus basic understanding of **Algorithms** and **Data Structure**.

Understanding of Java, Python Languages and OOP paradigm.

Experience with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects

EDUCATION

High Institute of Computer Science , Alexandria — Information Systems *Degree*

2017 - 2021

PROJECTS

Web based: <u>Portofolio</u> / <u>Fawaterk</u> / <u>Spotify Data Visualization</u> / <u>Blackklist</u> Android based: <u>Chattin</u> / <u>Twitterater</u>

EXPERIENCE

Technical Support at UX Centers - Borg El Arab, Alexandria, Egypt

September 2019 - February 2020

Responsibilities include diagnosing and repairing faults, resolving network issues.

Backend Developer at Fawaterk - 6 October, Egypt

June 2018 - September 2018

Was responsible for turning the code base for the platform from CakePHP to Laravel 5.6, plus adding new features.

Full Stack Developer at Upwork.com

April 2017 - June 2018

Building web apps and eCommerce based on PHP and Laravel Framework plus some tweaks in the Frontend sometimes.

LANGUAGES

Fluent in Arabic and English, Beginner in German